export const heepData = {
    definition : "heap is a specialized tree-based data structure that satisfies the heap property. A heap is often implemented as an array, where the parent node of a child node is always stored at a specific index relative to the child. There are two main types of heaps: max heaps and min heaps.",
    operations : ["Insert: Add a new element to the heap.","Extract-Max (or Extract-Min): Remove the root node, which is the element with the highest (or lowest) value.","Increase-Key: Increase the value of an existing element.","Decrease-Key: Decrease the value of an existing element."],
    questions: [
        {
            title: "Kth Largest Element in a Stream",
            id:"703",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-a-stream/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0703/?h=703",
        },
        {
            title: "Last Stone Weight",
            id:"1046",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "hhttps://leetcode.com/problems/last-stone-weight/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1046/?h=1046",
        }, 
        {
            title: "K Closest Points to Origin",
            id:"973",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/k-closest-points-to-origin/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0973/?h=973",
        },
        {
            title: "Kth Largest Element in an Array",
            id:"215",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0215/?h=215",
        }, 
        {
            title: "Task Scheduler",
            id:"621",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/task-scheduler/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0621/?h=621",
        },
        {
            title: "Design Twitter",
            id:"355",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/design-twitter/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0355/?h=355",
        },
        {
            title: "Minimize Deviation in Array",
            id:"1675",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimize-deviation-in-array/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1675/?h=1675",
        },
        {
            title: "Maximum Subsequence Score",
            id:"2542",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-subsequence-score/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/2542/?h=2542",
        }, 
        {
            title: "Single-Threaded CPU",
            id:"1834",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/single-threaded-cpu/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1834/?h=1834",
        },
        {
            title: "Seat Reservation Manager",
            id:"1845",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/seat-reservation-manager/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1845/?h=1845",
        },
        {
            title: "Process Tasks Using Servers",
            id:"1882",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/process-tasks-using-servers/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1882/?h=1882",
        },
        {
            title: "Find the Kth Largest Integer in the Array",
            id:"1985",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-kth-largest-integer-in-the-array/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1985/?h=1985",
        },
        {
            title: "Reorganize String",
            id:"767",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reorganize-string/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0767/?h=767",
        },
        {
            title: "Maximum Performance of a Team",
            id:"1383",
            difficulty: "Hard",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-performance-of-a-team/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1383/?h=1383",
        },
        {
            title: "IPO",
            id:"502",
            difficulty: "Hard",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/ipo/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0502/?h=502",
        },
    ]
}